in view of the Endless Possibilities in
the future we need more flexible plans
to tackle every challenge in
life sunlife Hong Kong is now rolling
out the ESG focused Stellar
multicurrency
plan which comes with long-term savings
and wealth growth potential to provide
you with stable returns and long lasting
income growth different premium payment
terms are available at your choice to
help you accumulate wealth effectively
the plan also offers the Currency Change
option you may switch between four
policy currencies flexibly to cope with
different life plans of you and your
family take the 35-year-old Mr Chan as
an example he has a family of three with
a three-year-old son Mr and Mrs Chan are
already getting prepared for their
retired life through sunlife Hong Kong
Stellar multicurrency plan they pay
$8,000 as premium every year which will
make a total of
$96,000 in 12 years years 3 years later
their daughter is born Mr and Mrs Chan
now want to save money for both kids so
they can study abroad in the future with
the help of Stellar multicurrency plan
Mr Chan splits his policy into three new
policies one accounting for 50% and the
other two for 25% each then Mr Chan
exercises the change of insured option
by changing the insured of the two split
policies 25% each to his two kids
respectively
Mr Chan can also exercise the Currency
Change option and the crossborder
payment service to make flexible
Financial plans for his kids to go to
Canada the UK or any other countries in
the
future the new split policy for Mr Chan
himself accounts for 50% of the original
policy during his retirement between the
ages of 65 and 84 he can withdraw
$4,800 a year being 10% of the total
premiums paid of the new policy that is
$96,000 in total and the total surrender
value at the time is
$535
1815 the total withdrawn amount and
total surrender value are equivalent to
13.16 times of the total premiums paid
for the new policy if needed you may
exercise the change of insured and
change of coverage options of your
policy for unlimited times Stellar
multicurrency plan even offers waiver of
premium benefit payer benefit and
premium holiday option you need not
worry about payment for premiums in case
of emergency you can even designate a
family member to file claims on your
behalf when you're diagnosed as a
mentally incapacitated person without
going through complicated legal
processes so that you will get support
immediately the plan offers six
comprehensive death benefit settlement
options for you to pass on your love to
your family in the most suitable
way the ESG focused Stellar
multicurrency plan is highly flexible it
helps you achieve wealth accumulation
and growth easily and pass on your love
and blessings to the Next
[Music]
Generation